comicpunch.net 2019-08-29

# Read Privacy Policy comic online | Comicpunch.net

How we collect and use personal information  
Comicpunch.net does not gather any of your personal data. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies." data-share-imageurl="">

Comicpunch.net is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible.   

How we collect and use personal information  

Comicpunch.net does not gather any of your personal data. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.  

How we protect your personal information  

All personal data you enter on Comicpunch.net is stored on our secure server protected by hardware and software firewalls at a limited access datacenter.  

How we use "cookies"  

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer’s hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, Comicpunch.net uses cookies to identify members so they don’t have to enter a user ID and password upon each visit. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis.  

What we provide to third parties  

While Comicpunch.net does not provide any third-party access to your personal information because we do not gather any of your personal data.  

Comicpunch.net uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. This company may use information about your visits to our and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   

In addition, we share Web site usage information about visitors to our site with these companies for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites. For this purpose, we and our third-party advertising companies note some of the pages you visit on our sites through the use of pixel tags (also called "clear gifs"). In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser.  

If you would like more information about the information collection practices of these third-party advertising companies or would like to know more about your option to not have this information used by these companies or to "opt-out", click here:  
<http://cpmstar.me/index.aspx?nav=privacy>  

Obtaining your consent  

By using our Web site, you give Comicpunch.net permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. By visiting Comicpunch.net, you authorize Comicpunch.net to use the browsing information gathered from your visit to providethe information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data.  

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law. Comicpunch.net does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.  

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
